idotz.net 2019-08-07

# iDotz.Net - Domain Name Registrar: Search.. Name.. Succeed!

Privacy Policy

We're updating our Privacy Policy on May 25, 2018. Our new policy and old policy are both below.

This is our updated Privacy Policy which went into effect on May 25, 2018.

___________________

Who We Are  

BRS Media, Inc. provides Online Services like Domains, DNS, Hosting and Streaming services via dot.FM, dot.AM, dotRadio, Get.fm, iDotz.Net, iRRP.Net, IDdp.Net, Webz.Net, HostRock.Net, MainStBranding.com, MainStreetBranding.com, DigitalAM.com and iRadio.com.

This privacy policy applies to all visitors and customers using or accessing any of the websites that we produced and maintain for the services that we provide, including dot.fm, dot.am, radio.fm, radio.am, get.fm, idotz.net, irrp.net, iddp.net, webz.net, hostrock.net, mainstbranding.com, digitalam.com and iradio.com. It also applies to human resources data of our employees and contractors.

This policy DOES NOT cover websites that we host for our customers as part of HostRock.net or iRRP.Net. For these sites, the site owner/customer is responsible for publishing its own privacy policy.

BRS Media, Inc. is a registered corporation in California, USA. Our mailing address is:

BRS Media, Inc.  
350 Townsend Street Suite 321  
San Francisco, CA 94107-1696  
USA

For any privacy-related questions, you can reach us at admin@brsmedia.com.

Who We Share Your Data With

We use third-party services (data processors) across our sites. The extent to which your data is shared with these providers depends on your use of our services, and we list the specific third-parties in use (with links to their privacy policies) in the sections below.

Effective May 25, 2018, As a registrar/reseller for ccTLD (Country Code Top-Level Domains) & ICANN TLD (Top-Level Domains) domain names, we will NO LONGER submit any information about you available to the general public via the registry domain name look-up and directory "whois" service (e.g., name, address, telephone and email of the Registrant), unless the TLD you are ordering mandates the direct contact information. i.e. ccTLD .CA (CANADA) & .US (UNITED STATES). IDDP.Net, LLC - ID Domain Privacy Network will be used for all domain name registrations across all BRS Media direct retail domain services.

As the registry for all .fm domain names and registry gaetway for .am domain names, With regards to WHOIS data, we will implement Registry Privacy Services redacting such information to protect Personal Data. 

Each third-party provider has been vetted by our security team to ensure that privacy policies and practices meet or exceed the same levels of compliance and standards that we follow. Where appropriate and available, we hold additional signed Data Privacy Agreements with these companies as an additional layer of accountability in order to help ensure your data is safe and secure.

We disclose potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to our employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf or to provide services, and (ii) that have agreed, in writing, not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using our websites and services, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. We will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone.

Business Transfers. We may disclose or transfer information, including personal information, as part of any merger, sale, and transfer of our assets, acquisition or restructuring of all or part of our business, bankruptcy, or similar event.

We may be required to disclose an individual's personal information in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

If we ever were to engage in any onward transfers of your data with third parties for a purpose other than which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized, we would provide you with an opt-out choice to limit the use and disclosure of your personal data.

Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. We use cookies across our sites to help identify and track visitors, their usage of our services, and their website access preferences. We describe the specific cookies used in the sections below. Visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using our websites, with the drawback that certain features may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

What Personal Data We Collect And Why We Collect It

Registered Users

If you create an account on one of our sites, you will be prompted to select a Username and provide your Email Address.

When choosing a Username, we strongly advise you not use or include your real name. Usernames cannot be changed.

Your Username and Email Address are stored in the website's database. Your Email Address is used to send you an email with a link to set your password or to send you an email with a link to reset your password in the event you forget your password.  
Once an account is created, you must contact us to have it deleted.

Accounts have a numeric User ID assigned to them when they are created. The User ID cannot be changed.

For some services you may be required to complete your Profile (example: Domain Names Service) by providing your First Name, Last Name, Address, City, State, County. These additional details are also saved in the website's database. You may edit these details, and your Email Address, in your Profile at any time.

We collect the following information about you:

  * full name

  * physical address

  * phone number

  * email address

  * IP address

  * cookies (see below)

  * payment information, including credit card details

  * identity verification documents

  * emails or other correspondence relating to the services you receive from us

  * internal notes about the services you receive from us

 * Cookies are small data files that our website sends to your browser, which are then stored on your system for later retrieval. We only use cookies to give you a simpler and easier login experience -- not to track your website use. Remember, you can always clear cookies locally in your browser.

Your Username, First Name, Last Name and Email Address are accessible by employees on the site.

If you attempt to log in to our site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies at all. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

If you have an account and you log in to a site, we will set up several cookies to save your login information and some of your screen options. The logged-in cookies last for two days, and the screen options cookies last for a year.

If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed. It is important that you log out if you are using a public computer.

For users that register on one of our sites, we also store the data they provide in their profile indefinitely. All registered users can see, change or delete most of that data at any time except their login name/nickname.

Email/Chat/Contact Forms

We use Google/G Suite to process all internal email and communication with our customers. Google's privacy policy is available here.

Customers that email us, or use any of the contact forms on our websites, will have their email address, IP address, and any data provided in the contact form or body of the email stored in G Suite archives and in our help desk third-party service provider, Kayako. 

We use Kayako to provide live chat and live support services. Any data provided during a live chat session with one of our team members will be recorded and logged in an email that is sent to our support help desk. This includes your name, email address, and IP address. The Kayako privacy policy is [found here](https://www.kayako.com/about/privacy).

Kayako uses cookies to tailor chat sessions to the individual. No personal information is stored in these cookies (only visit history). Cookies expire in 3 years.

We keep all email and chat communication indefinitely to help us provide support and improve our services. Individuals can request copies of any previous correspondence with us at any time.  

Embedded Content From Other Websites

Embeds are pieces from other websites that are shown from time to time on our websites. They behave in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website and may use cookies or capture information. Typically embedded content is from websites that share videos, images, or other content. These services may collect your IP Address, your User Agent, store and retrieve cookies on your browser, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including correlating your interaction with the content with your account with that service, if you are logged in to that service.

Links to the privacy policies of the most common services have been included below. Where a general privacy policy is not available, the applicable country is indicated.

Analytics

We use Google Analytics for tracking visitors and aggregating information about the traffic to our websites. The Google Analytics privacy policy can be found here: <https://policies.google.com/privacy>. You can learn more about how to opt-out of tracking in Google Analytics [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

Marketing Campaigns

We use email marketing and surveys to communicate with customers and potential customers from time to time. All email lists and campaigns are "opt-in" meaning we will not send you these sorts of emails unless you indicated that you wish to receive them during signup or other interactions on our website.   
We use Affiliate Marketing Network to communicate with customers and potential customers from time to time. We use ShareASale services for affiliate marketing. ShareASale's privacy policy is found [here](https://www.shareasale.com/PrivacyPolicy.pdf).     
We may send you "system" emails, such as password reset requests or payment notifications/receipts even if you have not opted-in to email marketing lists.  
All marketing emails sent by us will include an unsubscribe link in the footer of the email. Emails sent to you may also include standard tracking, including open and click activities.  
We use MailChimp services for email marketing. Mailchimp's privacy policy is found [here](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/). We use SurveyMonkey services for online surveys. SurveyMonkey's privacy policy is found [here](https://www.surveymonkey.com/mp/legal/privacy-policy/). We may utilize social media and web advertising campaigns. These service providers use cookies on our sites and/or pixel tracking to serve ads across the different platforms.

Google AdSense & DoubleClick ([privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) | [opt out](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en))  
Twitter ([privacy policy](https://twitter.com/en/privacy) | [opt out](https://help.twitter.com/en/safety-and-security/privacy-controls-for-tailored-ads))  
Facebook ([privacy policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy) | [opt out](https://www.facebook.com/help/146952742043748?helpref=related))

Paying Customers

For payment transactions, we use PayPal, BitPay and Skrill. PayPal's privacy policy can be found [here](https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full). Bitpay's privacy policy can be found [here](https://bitpay.com/about/privacy). Skill's privacy policy can be found [here](https://www.skrill.com/en/footer/privacypolicy/).  
To comply with accounting and legal requirements, we keep data on financial transactions in the systems above for up to 10 years.

Hosting and API Services

All web servers and hosting are managed by our team on the Media3 Cloud and/or Amazon Web Services platform located in different regions around the world. This includes website hosting, backups, web database, file storage, APIs, and log files. Media3's privacy policy can be found [here](https://support.media3.net/?pageid=1037). Amazon's privacy policy can be found [here](http://www.amazon.com/privacy).

What Rights You Have Over Your Data

If you are a registered user on our site you can request to see or download the data we have about you.

For registered users or paying customers, this will include profile information and download, payment, and support ticket histories.

You can also request "to be forgotten" and we will erase any personally identifiable data we have about you. Of course, this excludes data we need for administrative or security purposes or if we are required by law to retain some of the data.

An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data, should direct his/her query to admin@brsmedia.com. We will respond within a reasonable timeframe, not to exceed 10 working days.

How We Protect Your Data

The security and reliability of our service is our number one priority.

Prevention is best when it comes to security, and as a first step, we follow all Code Standards in the platforms that we build and use.  
In addition, we have an extensive internal review and Quality Assurance process in place specifically to prevent potential security vulnerabilities in our platforms and services.  
Every employee and contractor goes through background and onboarding process that includes a trial period where access to customer data is provided only when working directly under the supervision of another staff member.  
All staff only have access to systems that are directly required to complete the functions of their job. We use dual factor authentication for all critical systems and communications services, and automatically log all staff activity using an internal logging tool, Google G' Suite features, and Amazon Cloud Trail.  
All staff (including any contractors) undergo initial training to ensure proper understanding of all security-related processes. Staff regularly attend industry conferences and otherwise stay informed of best practices and relevant trends. Staff review and agree, in writing, to all policies and procedures annually.  
We only use third-party services, such as Amazon Web Services, that are fully vetted and adhere to the highest levels of privacy and security practices.

Security Policy

How We Protect Information about our Customers

Industry-standard SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption (https://) is always used to protect your purchase information while in transit.  
Stored credit card information is always encrypted and maintained in an environment that has been certified as PCI DSS compliant by a qualified security assessor.  
BRS Media websites are constantly scanned and validated to verify application and network security.  
All internal security standards, policies and practices are frequently reviewed and improved based on the current industry security practices.

What Data Breach Procedures We Have In Place

Should any event occur where customer data has been lost, stolen, or potentially compromised, our policy is to alert our customers via email no later than 48 hours of our team becoming aware of the event. We will also report such incident to any required data protection authority. We will work closely with any customers affected to determine next steps such as any end-user notifications, needed patches, and how to avoid any similar event in the future.

Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, BRS Media may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in BRS Media's sole discretion.

Changelog

May 25, 2018 - Updated language of the policy to be more user-friendly, specifically outlining requirements in preparation for meeting the GDPR.  
__________________

  **iDotz.Net™ Privacy Policy  
   **(effective July 1, 2002) 

  This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting our Web site or by otherwise interacting with dotFM, you agree to accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. For questions on the Privacy Policy please contact 

[privacy@idotz.net](mailto:privacy@idotz.net).

  Your privacy is very important to iDotz.Net, a division on BRS Media Inc., which owns all information collected from the site and is a registrar of domain names. iDotz.Net also offers other supplementary products and services (the "Service"). We recognize your right to confidentiality and are committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy statement describes how we collect information, how we use the information we collect, and to whom and under what conditions we may disclose this information. This statement reflects our concern with your privacy. Please understand that the following statement applies to www.idot.net only. 

  When you use our Service, iDotz.Net asks for your first and last name, organization, city, state, zip code (or country and postal code for non-U.S. residents), telephone number, e-mail address, and credit card information. We may use this personally identifiable information to contact you about your account or other matters relating to the Service, such as to inform you about new features on our Site. We may also use this personally identifiable information to send you our newsletter or e-mail messages regarding products or services we think you might be interested in. (See below for instructions on how you can "opt out" of our newsletter or these e-mail messages.) These communications are essential to our relationship with you and to our ability to provide you with quality products and services that are responsive to your needs. At the same time, these communications, and your responses to them, give us helpful insights about you, your preferences and the ways in which we might improve our services. We therefore may maintain this information for future use. When you utilize the Service, we may also ask you for a "screen name." Although we may not use it now, the screen name you select may appear on the web site in connection with future services we provide. 

  Like many other commercial web sites, our Site employs a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how our Site is used, such as which pages are the most frequently visited by our customers. "Cookies" are small pieces of electronic information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies enable our systems to recognize your browser and provide personalized information and features such as pre-populated address forms and storage of selected items in your Shopping Cart between visits. Cookies are required for normal website functionality, and most web browsers automatically accept cookies, although you can usually change your browser to deactivate cookies by modifying your computer browser preferences. If you choose to deactivate cookies, please note that deactivation of cookies will sometimes hinder your ability to use some features available from the Service. Through the use of cookies, we take note of whether and how you use the information and services that we provide, such as by recording site traffic patterns and by maintaining log files of your access to various parts of the Site. We may collect the information passed along by your web browser that references the Web URL you linked from, the time, type of web browser being used, screen size, Internet speed of connection, the operating system/platform, and CPU speed. This information may be used to identify demographic trends and to provide information tailored to your interests. 

  Cookies may also be utilized by third parties who advertise or provide links on the Site. Due to the way the Internet technically operates, iDotz.Net cannot the control data collection activities by such third-party advertisers or linked web sites. You should contact these advertisers or web site operators if you have any questions about their use of the information they collect. Also, if you register a domain name through another registrar, you may receive a cookie from that registrar, but you will not receive a cookie from us. 

Registrants may elect not to receive e-mail communications from iDotz.Net regarding other products or services provided by iDotz.Net or BRS Media Inc. To do so, please send an email to 

[privacy@idotz.net](mailto:privacy@idotz.net) that reads, "Remove from E-mail List." You can also fax us at +1 (415) 677-4025 or send us mail at:

BRS Media Inc.  
Attention: iDotz.Net Opting Out  
350 Townsend Street Suite 321  
San Francisco, CA 94107-1696

 iDotz.Net understands that security is important to our users. The information we receive from or about you is stored on systems designed to prevent the loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of that information. When you transmit personal information to us, we encrypt it using SSL (Secure Socket Layer), the industry standard for encryption software. Encryption provides a secure means to protect your information as it passes over the web to our server. iDotz.Net utilizes Thawte SSL Web Server Certificates to offer secure communications by encrypting all data to and from the site. You can verify this certificate by clicking here: 

iDotz.Net Certificate

 iDotz.Net will use commercially available and acceptable means to protect any information you provide, but cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us from our products and services, and you do so at your own risk. iDotz.Net will not be liable for disclosures of your personal information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties.

  As the registrar of domain names, we may make certain information about you available to the general public via our domain name look-up and directory "whois" service (e.g., name, address, telephone and email of the Registrant). Additionally, we may share the information stored on that database, as well as other information we collect or you provide, with our subsidiaries and other parties selected by us, including with the parties or circumstances including, but not limited to: 

   · Agents or vendors who are responsible for handling your Account or performing  
     other necessary service that you or we require. 

   · Business partners whose services you may request or access on or through our  
     Site. 

   · Business partners or vendors who we believe offer products or services that may  
     be of interest to you. 

   · Transfer of ownership of our business or a part of our business. If our business  
     or a part of our business is acquired, sold or transferred to another business,  
     customer information may be a part of that acquisition, sale or transfer. 

 _Protection of iDotz.Net and Others_ : We may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable account information if required to do so by law, subpoena, search warrant, court order or other government or law enforcement authority or regulatory agency, including ICANN; to enforce or apply our Services Agreement or other agreements; or when we believe in good faith that disclosing this information is necessary or advisable, including, for example, to protect the rights, property, or safety of BRS Media Inc., iDotz.Net, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

 If you do not want us to share personally identifiable information about you with our business partners or vendors, you may send us e-mail at 

[ privacy@idotz.net](mailto:privacy@idotz.net). You may not opt out from having your personal information displayed in our "whois" database.

  We may enter into agreements to allow third party registrars of domain. When users register domain names through these third party registrars, we will transfer the registration information collected during the registration process to the domain Registry. We may also be required to submit this information to ICANN (Internet Corporation for Assigned Names and Numbers), or other regulatory bodies.

  Although iDotz.Net is committed to protecting your privacy, not all other Web sites are as conscientious. Therefore, iDotz.Net cannot be responsible for the content or privacy policies of other Web sites including those of advertisers to which it may link and those which link to iDotz.Net. This Privacy Policy applies only to the information collected by this Web site. We ask that you review the privacy policies of every online service you use before submitting personal information. 

  We welcome your feedback. If you have questions or comments about our privacy policies, please feel free to send us an e-mail at 

[privacy@idotz.net](mailto:privacy@idotz.net) or by mail at:

BRS Media Inc.  
Attention: iDotz.Net Privacy Policy  
350 Townsend Street Suite 321  
San Francisco, CA 94107-1696
